> > Jem Young: 那是一次冒险，是一次巨大的冒险。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: That was an adventure,
that was a big adventure.
所以希望你有它的承诺你现在可以在这里工作了
So hopefully, you've got it committed,
you can now work on it,
任何人都可以使用它，你可以把你的服务器推给你的心脏内容。
anybody can work on it, you can tweak
your server to your heart's content.
我们做到了，就是第一天。
And we did it, that was day one.
那么， recap，我们学到了什么 ?
So recap, what did we learn?
我们学会了互联网的运作。
We learned how the Internet works.
我们学会如何将 IP 连接到一个域，
We learned how to connect an IP
to a domain, to a server,
到 Web 服务器，到应用程序服务器，并提供数据。
to a web server, to an application server,
and serve out data.
我们学会了如何配置 Nginx ，我们学会了如何配置 Git 。
We learned how to configure Nginx a bit,
we learned how to configure Git a bit.
[LAUGH] 如果需要进一步的浏览，那么可以安装 Fail2ban。
[LAUGH] If you want some further
exploration, you can install Fail2ban.
Fail2ban，您是否还记得我们如何解决认证日志，以及
Fail2ban, do you remember earlier
how we solve the auth log, and
就像人们总是想进入我的服务器
like people always trying
to get in my server?
Fail2ban 是一个日志包，本质上它读了很多次尝试，所以
Fail2ban is a log parcel essentially
that it reads a lot of attempts, so
如果有人尝试登录五次无效，就会被禁止
if someone attempts to login five times
it's invalid, it's gonna ban them
所以如果你愿意的话你甚至都不能给你一个有效的登录
completely, so you can't even give
a valid login if you want to.
这对停止脚本是有用的
And that's useful for
stopping script those
就是下载脚本的人，然后在很多网站上运行这些脚本。
are people that just download scripts and
then run them against lots of websites.
Fail2ban 很有用，我不参加这个课程，虽然我以前是，
Fail2ban is pretty useful, I don't go into
it in this course, even though I used to,
就因为学习，可能没那么重要。
just because for learning,
it's probably not that important.
但如果你把它送到真正的生产服务器
But if you're sending it for
real production server,
你就会一直想有 " 故障 " 或类似的东西
you're almost gonna always wanna
have Fail2ban or something similar.
如果你想做快车
And if you wanna do Express,
Express.js 在性能提示方面的站点非常好。
Express.js has a really good
site on performance tips.
它告诉你如何调整一个 Nginx 的位置，如何设置高速缓存，
So it tells you how to tune an Nginx
a bit, how to set up caching,
告诉你关于清柒的事
tells you all about varnish,
Nginx 高速缓存告诉您如何正确设置标题，类似的内容。
Nginx caching, tells you how to set up
the headers correctly, things like that.
那也就是读书的好，你想和 Express 就开始乱搞了
That's good reading too, if you want
to start messing about with Express and
你以前没有过
you have not before.
但现在我们已经到了最后
But now, we're at the end, so
你现在有更多精力了我现在就在这里
you have a lot more energy now cuz i
started off here and now I'm about here,
因为我每天都是一个晚上 100% 的人，我在晚上做最好的编码。
because I'm a night person a 100% all day,
I do my best coding at night.
有问题吗
Are there any questions?
你想知道更多的事吗
Anything you wanna know more about?
>> 扬声器 2: 我不知道这是否会花费太多时间，但我除去了
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I don't know if this will
take up too much time, but I removed my
节点模块，现在我在想如何创建该 git 忽略文件?
node modules, and now I'm wondering
how to create that git ignore file?
>> Jem Young: So vi.gitignore。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So vi.gitignore.
>> 演讲者 2:
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Mm-hm.
>> Jem Young: 你在那里也有管理吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Did you manage
it there as well, sir?
>> 演讲者 3: 是的，我创造了这个，现在我只是在努力推动。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah, I created that,
now I'm just stuck trying to push.
>> Jem Young: [LAUGH] 我可以来看看你的电脑
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: [LAUGH]
I may come just look at your computer,
我们就能看到我们的位置了
we'll see where we're at.
>> 扬声器 2: 然后，我将放置节点模型
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: And
then I would put the node models
在此 - >> Jem Young: 是，
in there-
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes,
添加节点下划线模块斜杠- >> 演讲者 2: 斜杠，好吗 ?
you add node underscore modules slash-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Slash, okay?
>> Jem Young: 现在，只要除去这些节点模块，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: For now, as long as
you remove those node modules and
将更改向上推送到 Github，然后添加 git 忽略 firs，
push that change up to Github,
and then add the git ignore firs,
取决于你做的事情
it depends on the order you did things.
>> 扬声器 2: 是，除去它们，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, remove them,
我加了这个，然后我该 [INAUDIBLE] 吗 ?
I'm adding this, and
then should I [INAUDIBLE] after this?
>> Jem Young: 是的，让它继续运行。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah,
to keep it up and running.
>> 扬声器 2: 嗯，好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, all right.
> > Jem Young: 那么一点点的回忆，我们学到的不是什么魔法
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So a bit of a recap,
we learned that it's not magic between
前端和后端实际上是大量的胶水工作。
the frontend and the backend,
in fact, it's a lot of glue work.
很多被低估的工作都是由域连接构成的
It's a lot of underappreciated work
that goes from making a domain connect
到服务器，并且该服务器发出应用程序。
to a server, and
that server serve out an application.
事实上，我们学到的是互联网是如何运作的，
And in fact, what we learned
was how the Internet works,
我们发现有一个域通过名称服务器来查找 IP 地址。
we learned that there's a domain that
looks up the IP address via name server.
名称服务器将返回到节点的 IP ，并且节点将关闭，
The name server returns the IP that passes
off to a node, and the node passes off,
把它关了，然后把它关掉，最后击中一个服务器。
and pass it off, and pass it off,
and eventually hits a server.
那台服务器说，我想做些什么呢 ?
That server says, what do I want
do this quest we tried to go?
然后它会传递到一个 web 服务器，那就是昨天 Nginx 的服务器。
And then it passes off to a web server,
that was server is Nginx yesterday.
然后它就会传递给应用服务器
And then it passes to
an application server,
应用程序服务器是 Express.js，我们都在那里降落。
and the application server was Express.js,
that's where we all landed.
如果你想的是很多话，就做这个，对，就是。
And if you're thinking that was a lot
of words, just do this, yeah, it is.
但今天我们要用更快速的方法
But today, we're gonna learn
some faster ways of doing this,
我们不必每次都手动执行此操作。
some ways that we don't have to do
this manually every single time.
但就像往常一样，如果你在学习一些东西，那么手动步骤是好的
But as always, if you're learning
something, it's good to go manually step
让你明白我们是怎么做的
by step by step, so
you understand exactly what we do.
昨天我们还学会了一些指挥线路，
Yesterday we also learned
some command line basic,
我们有点眼熟我们没怎么用鼠标
we came a little familiar,
we didn't use the mouse as much.
如果你是个 UI 工程师你应该用鼠标
And if you're an UI engineer,
you probably use the mouse
你每天都能做的最不一样的
the least of all you ever did possible for
an entire day.
我们还学会了互联网是如何运作的，我们学会了如何创造和
We also learned how the Internet works,
we learned how to create and
管理 Web 服务器，并且我们创建了一个基本的基本节点应用程序。
manage web server, and we created
a pretty basic node application.
今天我们要做一些更先进的事情
Today, we're gonna do things that
are a bit more advanced, and
我有个最后的项目我想这会很有趣的
I have a final projects,
I think it's gonna be pretty fun.
[ INAUDIBLE] 酒店房间点 JS 因为我上次在酒店房间写的
[INAUDIBLE] hotel room dot JS because
I wrote it last time at hotel room,
我想我们会有很多乐趣的
I think we're gonna have
a lot of fun with it.
但现在，我们有了共同的底线，所以我们可以做一些更多的事情，
But now, we have this common baseline,
so we can do things that are a bit more,
我想说有趣的是我不想做第一部分
I wanna say interesting cuz that I
don't wanna make the first part,
看起来有点迟钝但会更先进些
it seem a little dull but
they'll be a bit more advanced.